Md. Asaduzzaman (Aminur)

Assistant Web Designer/Developer Diploma in Engineering (CSE)

\(+88 01719 670601

■ aminur670601@gmail.com

aminur670.github.io

in linkedin.com/in/aminur670

aithub.com/Aminur670

🕈 Komaygari, Naogaon Sadar- 6500, Rajshahi, Bangladesh



Career Objective

To build up a long-term career development and looking for a challenging career in a dynamic situation where there is a scope for demonstration, thrive to imagination and passion to reach in esteem level.

Career Summary

Excellent skilled & motivated in computer professional with more than 2 years of experience over several sector in the IT field of local and global. Gathered knowledge over Corporate IT sector, and Technical Support with successful implementation of it. Gather good experience of Programming, Web/App Design and Develop, eCommerce & It Supports etc.

Employment History

Years of Employment Experience: 2+ Years

✓ Assistant Web Developer (Jan,2021 – Jul,2021):

Faith Media LTD.

https://faithmedialtd.com

Location: 29th Street, Mohakhali DOHS, Dhaka.



Department: Web Design & Development, IT

Duties/Responsibilities:

- ✓ Making WordPress sites with Elementor as approved design as client requirement.
- ✓ Making Project Models & plans for smooth team workflow
- ✓ Developing Website/Web Application & UML/Features Models as client requirement
- ✓ Products Data/Image upload & update to eCommerce website
- ✓ Product Image Retouch & Editing, Product Listing,
- ✓ Finding e-commerce site's issue & notify to team
- ✓ Promotional & offers email template creating for products
- ✓ Office email support, email marketing with provided mailing list

√ Virtual IT Assistant of CEO (Jan,2020 – Dec,2020):

TIC Accessories LTD.

https://ticaccessoriesltd.com

Location: 167th Street, Jamaica, New York 11432, USA.



Department: Ecommerce Site

Duties/Responsibilities:

- ✓ Promotional & offers email template creating for products
- ✓ Office email support, email marketing with provided mailing list
- ✓ eBay, amazon, e-commerce stores managing & support
- \checkmark Finding e-commerce site's issue & notify to developers
- ✓ Collecting new/old products data/image and upload/update to eBay, amazon, e-commerce stores
- ✓ Social media page & profile management & support
- ✓ Documents, letters, agreement drafting, product photo editing, pdf editing etc... Support.
- ✓ Google sheet managing for company several sector
- ✓ Data entry & provide training to new employees & clients
- ✓ Web scraping & research as needed
- ✓ Software & hardware trouble shooting
- ✓ IT consultation to admin section

✓ IT Trainer & ICT Teacher (Jul,2019 - Dec,2019):

EEE & IT Engineering Training Center

Location: Mondol Mor, Sapahar-6560, Naogaon, Rajshahi.

Department: ICT & IT (SSC & HSC)

Duties/Responsibilities:

- ✓ Taking classes:
 - ➤ Programming for of 6th -12th Class, Basic256, C/C++ & OOP
 - ➤ Basics of HTML, CSS, JS, PHP, MySQL Database
- ✓ Perform theory & practical classes.
- ✓ Making presentation for interactive classes.
- ✓ Maintain and addressing about IT related issue.



• •		
Company	Work Session	Duration
Faith Media Ltd (Assistant Web Designer/Developer) 29th Street, Mohakhali DOHS, Dhaka.	Jan,2021 – July,2021	7 months
TIC Accessories Inc. (Virtual IT Assistant of CEO) 167th Street, Jamaica, New York 11432, USA	Jan,2020 – Dec,2020	1 year
EEE & IT Training Center (ICT Teacher & Trainer) Mondol Mor, Sapahar-6560, Naogaon, Rajshahi	Jul,2019 - Dec,2019	6 months

Projects Experience

Website/Clients	Category	Contribution & supports in projects	Link
Faith Media Ltd.	Agency	Full WP Development, Content Update	faithmedialtd.com
Faith Overseas	Agency	Content Update	faithoverseasbd.com
Gontobbo Xpress	Delivery System	Full WP Development, Content Update	gontobboxpress.com
Real Café	Agency	Full WP Development, Content Update	realcafebd.com
Different Café	Agency	Full WP Development, Content Update	differentcafebd.com
ChemByNavid	E-education	Partial WP Development, Content Update	chembynavid.com



IFSDL	Agency	Partial WP Development	ifsdl.com
Rongtuli	E-commerce	Product Data & Image Support & Upload	rongtuli.net/shop
Tholay	E-commerce	Product Data & Image Support & Upload	tholay.xyz
TIC Accessories Inc	E-commerce	Product Data & Image Support & Upload	ticaccessoriesltd.com
Rapid Supplies Inc	E-commerce	Full WP Development, Content Update	rapidsupplies.xyz
Faith Xpress	Delivery System	Vue3+Laravel, Model, Development (on-develop)	faithexpress.xyz
NTSC	School/Collage	Vue3+Laravel, UI Design, develop(on-develop)	ntsc.vercel.io
Auto Bell System	School/Collage	C#.net & Sqlite3 Project for Bogura Polytechnic Ins.	

Academic Qualification				
Exam Title & Major Subject	Institute	Result	Pass	Duration
Diploma in Engineering, Computer Technology	Bogura Polytechnic Institute, Bogura	2.92 out of 4	2018	4 Years
S.S.C. (Voc) Computer Department	Naogaon Technical School & Collage, Naogaon-6500	4.88 out of 5	2013	2 Years

ľ	❖ Professional Training Summary				
	Training Title	Institute	Location	Year	Duration
	Web Design & Development	Bangladesh IT Institute	Parbota, Mirpur-10,	2017	3 Months
		(BITI)	Dhaka-1216		

❖ Self-Learning & Independent Professional Training Summary			
Title	Course Time	Year	Duration
C/C++, C#.net & OOP	07-12-2016 to 1-06-2016	2016	6 Months
Python & OOP, Linux Operating System	01-01-2016 to 1-06-2017	2016	6 Months
Web Design & Development	05-06-2017 to 06-12-2017	2017	6 Months
WordPress (Elementor-Design + Plugin)	03-01-2018 to 20-06-2018	2018	6 Months
Laravel, C-Panel & Hosting System	06-06-2020 to 12-01-2021	2021	6 Months
Inertia, Vue3, Axios, Rest Api	25-01-2021 to 15-06-2021	2021	6 Months

❖ Programming & Skills

- ✓ HTML, CSS, JavaScript, Bootstrap, jQuery, Web Image/Icons/Fonts, VueJS-3, InertiaJS, AxiosJS, Rest Api
- ✓ PHP, MySQL & SQLite3 Database, Laravel, C-Panel & Web Hosting, Git
- ✓ WordPress Customization (WordPress + Custom Design with Elementor + Plugin)
- ✓ Programming Languages: C/C++ (OOP), C#.net (OOP), Python3 (OOP), PHP, JS SLQi
- ✓ Microsoft Office 2016 (Word, PowerPoint, Excel, Outlook, OneNote)
- √ Graphics Design (Photoshop, Illustrator)
- ✓ Emailing, Letter/Documents/PDF/Agreement Editing/Drafting etc.
- ✓ Experience of Software & Hardware Problem Solving.

Activities and interests

- ✓ Good knowledge in programming languages (OOP & Procedural)
- ✓ Career oriented, hardworking and ability to handle multiple tasks
- ✓ Quick learner and ability to learn new concepts

Pivotal Cloud Foundry Platform (GitHub)

Strong collaboration skills

Excellent communication skills

Achievements

- Strong communication and interpersonal skills.
- Good analytical and problem-solving skills.
- Good Skill on Software Development across Platforms & Operation Systems.

Language Proficiency

✓ Fluent in reading, writing, speaking and understanding in both Bangla and English.

Personal Strengths

- Highly motivated, self-disciplined, good team organizer, and pleasantly adaptable.
- Always keen to take on responsibility and possess strong leadership qualities.
- Work under pressure at a fast pace and committed to professionalism.

Personal Information

<u>Biodata</u>		Permanent Address
Name	: Md. Asaduzzaman (Aminur)	Moholla: Hajrat Khaza Bakibillah (R.) Moholla
Father	: Md. Abul Kalam Azad	Village: Komaygari.
Mother	: Mst. Anju Ara	Post : Naogaon Sadar.
Birth Date	: 22/01/1997	District: Naogaon-6500.
Gender	: Male	Division: Rajshahi.
Height	: 5'9"	
Religion	: Islam	Present Address
Nationality	: Bangladeshi (By Birth)	Same as Permanent Address
National ID	: 19976426001000186	
		I .

* Reference			
Referance-1	Referance-2		
Md. Azizul Amin Al-Aman	Abdur Rahim		
Head of the Department (Computer Technology)	Manager (Dhaka Branch)		
Bogra Polytechnic Institute, Bogra-6500.	Alpha Net, Dhaka-1000, Bangladesh		
4 +880 1712 685203	L +880 1736 891765		

Asaduzzaman Date: 29 September 2021

Signature